It's time for another edition of Things I Learned this week.
Did you know that apparently elephants have been observed being aware of natural cycles
and they apparently practice moon worship, like waving branches at the moon
and engaging in ritual bathing when the moon is full.
I thought that was like really fascinating.
Did you know butterflies won't fly when it rains because the raindrops damage their wings?
I thought about it.
I was like, I've never seen a butterfly in the rain.
No, never.
It's like butterflies in the rain.
I know, right?
Did you know that dolphins can identify humans by checking their skeleton structure with their sonar?
They often help shipwreck victims fight sharks and stay afloat
because as a mammal, they understand drowning.
Wow, wow.
This is a bonus one.
There is a group that's like been studying like whales language and they had a 20-minute conversation with a whale.
The group did?
Yeah.
So they basically, a team of scientists, they played a humpback whale greeting call underwater and a whale responded
and they exchanged with him for 20 minutes.
It's considered extraterrestrial intelligence.
It's only a matter of time until they're going to be able to translate this stuff.
I mean, listen, when you see the dogs talking with the buttons, that right there is bugged out
and they'd be like, no, they're just saying anything.
No, I'd be following the dogs with the buttons.
They talking.